Among those in town with a Yanbei accent...
there's one other person.
It's her fellow townsman.
Her fellow townsman?
Who is it?
It's...
Master
Why can't I move?
Paper seller
It's you?
Why is it you again?
You two. You two.
Buy a newspaper?
The ancient book, Heavenly Craftsmanship,
hand it over to me,
and I'll spare your life.
Don't bother looking for me.
I was just looking for you too.
You have a Yanbei accent.
You're the Spirit Medium's fellow townsman.
Jiang Huai.
Looking for Heavenly Craftsmanship?
Heavenly Craftsmanship...
How did it end up in your hands?
This book
is your family's ancestral heirloom.
But you had no idea
that it hides a massive secret.
It's a waste to leave it in your hands.
So I stole the book,
and set a fire
to burn down your family's library.
Run!
Huai'er!
You set the fire!
You stole the book!
Tell me,
why did you burn our Wenchang Pavilion?
Heavenly Craftsmanship
is useless in your hands.
Treasures must be put to good use.
We were both the Warlord's servants then.
Before he died, the Warlord gave an order.
Amidst the warlord conflicts,
my Yanbei Army's forces were depleted.
If we want to make a comeback,
we must raise funds for the army.
Yes.
How should we raise the funds?
Please instruct us, Warlord.
A prince from the late Qing dynasty
and I are old acquaintances.
He said
his ancestors wrote a vault's location
in the book Heavenly Craftsmanship.
Heavenly Craftsmanship?
Where is this book now?
This book
is in the library at Wenchang Pavilion.
You must find this book
and revitalize the Yanbei Army.
Warlord! Warlord!
After the Warlord passed away,
we set the fire and stole the book,
heading south with Heavenly Craftsmanship.
But unexpectedly,
while the two of us were resting,
the book was stolen by thieves.
Later, we found out
it was the Four Thieves of Yanbei.
Hurry!
Eventually, the book ended up in Li Town,
in the hands of Master Li.
So,
we came to Li Town.
The Spirit Medium searched the Li Estate.
I searched the whole estate to no avail.
However,
I unexpectedly discovered
Chunmei, Dazhu, and Erzhu plotting.
They wanted to kill Master Li.
Since the book wasn't found,
Master Li couldn't die.
We had to find a way
to keep him alive.
Your plan was going smoothly at first.
But after we arrived in Li Town,
I was caught for a ghost marriage.
Brother Xun reported it,
and Mu Ying investigated.
The haunting case at the Li Estate
was about to be solved.
Seeing that you were
about to be caught in one swoop,
you feared Master Li would expose you.
So you ordered the Spirit Medium
to use the poison on the bracelet
to poison Master Li.
You feared the poison would be detected,
and trace the bracelet
back to the Spirit Medium,
so you snuck into the hospital with her
to steal the evidence.
The corpse has risen!
Master Li has risen from the dead!
The Spirit Medium disguised as Master Li,
successfully tricking Xun away.
Then you snuck in and attacked the doctor,
stealing the lab report and the bracelet.
To destroy the evidence,
you even brought Master Li's body
to burn at the gates of the Li Estate.
And then,
to end this once and for all,
you decided to poison the Spirit Medium.
We owe the Warlord everything.
The treasure must not fall to others.
After Master Li died,
the police will soon track us down.
Let's grab the book and get out of here.
Not so fast.
If we leave now,
Mu Ying will have her eyes on us.
We have to wait for things to cool down,
then we'll find a way to leave Li Town.
Our old fortune-telling scams
were all exposed by them.
We need a new trick from now on.
Let's use Spirit Summoning with Rice.
You know too much.
Only I can guard the treasure.
You used ink laced with aconitine
to print the newspaper.
Once the finger was cut,
the poison entered the bloodstream,
causing death.
Old man,
I don't know who you are,
but to keep the treasure for yourself,
you'd even murder your own accomplice.
Are you even human?
Mu Ying!
What the hell did you do to Mu Ying?
I installed a timing device
on the poison gas valve.
It opens every half hour.
The gas will grow thicker each time...
...until Mu Ying dies.
Jiang Huai.
You have the time for one incense stick.
Find the vault's location in the book.
If you dare call the police,
I'll kill Mu Ying right away.
Mu Ying!